bizymoms.com 2003-06-21

# Bizy Moms.com - Our Privacy Policy - The site for work at home information, ideas, and advice.

|  | 

|  | 

**_Bizymoms Privacy Policy  
_ ** ****

**This web site is owned by[Liz Folger](http://www.bizymoms.com/lizfolger.html).**

She can be reached via e-mail at [bizymoms@bizymoms.com](mailto:bizymoms@bizymoms.com)  
Or you can reach her by telephone at 530-938-2253.

Mailing Address: Bizymoms, 5828 Brook Ln., Weed, CA 96094

Bizymoms shares your concern for privacy online and has implemented the following privacy policy to make you aware of how your visit, and any information you share with us while on our site, is utilized.

**Secure Shopping:** When making a purchase on our web site your credit card information is requested on a secure server and is not retained after your sale has been completed. Your personal information is retained in a database for our sales records ONLY and will not be shared with any third parties. If you opt-in to be informed of future product releases we will retain your email address but it will not be shared with any third parties and will only be utilized to provide the information which you requested. You will not receive any unrequested promotions, communications or announcements without your permission.

**Chatting At Bizymoms:** When logging into our chat room you can choose the option of retaining your preferred name and color choice on your computer via a cookie. This is entirely optional and has been included as a service to you, to make your visit easier. Your chat name and color choice is not saved in any way on our servers. Bizymoms does log all chat activity in our chat room, these logs are used to share chat content with your fellow visitors who could not attend the chat, for security purposes so we can monitor the room for unacceptable behavior, and all logs are discarded after 14 days.

**Message Board Registration:** In order to post on our message boards you must be a registered member. This policy was implemented to decrease the amount of unacceptable posts on our boards, so that all members can enjoy the time they spend there. The information which you share during registration and in your profile is retained in our message board database, we do not use your information for any other purpose*. Be aware that the only required information is: your first name, email address, a user name, and a password. All other information in your profile is entirely optional and can be hidden or deleted by you at any time. 

* Unfortunately there are unscrupulous individuals out there who use special programs to gather email addresses on the internet without permission. If you notice an increase in spam after registering for the message boards it is due to these aforementioned unscrupulous people gathering your email address from your postings, NOT from your protected profile information. Unfortunately this problem exists on any site where people post messages or share their email address openly on the internet. Bizymoms is constantly monitoring the internet for new security features to prevent the gathering of email addresses on our site and will use new technology if/when it becomes available to protect you.

**Bizy News Subscriptions:** When you submit your email address to us for inclusion in our Bizy News email list your address is used solely to share news about our site. This news is delivered primarily through our Weekly Newsletter, but also may arrive in occasional special announcements about our site. Please see the information at the bottom of each mailing for easy instructions on how to unsubscribe if at any time you wish to stop receiving the mailings. Your email address will not be shared with any third parties or be used for any purpose other than those described in this section.

**Surfing Our Site:** While visiting Bizymoms our stat tracking software will gather information on which page you enter from, which page you leave from, and the pages you visit in our site. BUT you are not identified by any personal information (such as name, email address, street address, etc...) the only identification we receive is your IP address which is used to identify your movement through the site and can not be used to contact you. Your activity and IP address is not retained and is merely used by Bizymoms to guage page popularity, problems experienced when accessing pages, and for our own review to make improvements to our site. This information is not shared with any third parties or used in any other manner.

In addition we do rotate banners on the site. While most of our banners are local to our server a few are delivered by affiliate programs which may place a cookie on your computer to prevent your being counted as viewing their banners more than once, no personally identifiable information is retained by Bizymoms or our banner suppliers. Any cookies can easily be removed from your computer by reading your browser help file and there are programs available to automatically remove, or prevent the saving of cookies on your computer without your knowledge.

As the Bizymoms site grows and changes we hope you will rest assured that your personal privacy is always a high priority for us. Our promise to you is that we will continue to search for ways to protect your privacy while supplying you with a valuable and pleasant visit to our web site. We hope this privacy policy will put your mind at ease and help you to enjoy your time here.

**Thank You for visiting and we hope you will visit us often!**
